bandicam.com 2017-07-07

# Bandicam Company Privacy Policy

"Bandicam Company" respects your right to privacy. You may browse and access information contained in certain parts of this website without providing any personal information. However, some sections of this website require you to provide personal information in order to provide services that you request, and so the following privacy statement explains collection, dissemination and use of your personal data in those situations. This information may be expanded or updated as we change or develop our site. For this reason, we recommend that you review this policy from time to time to see if anything has changed. 

## Cookies

"Bandicam Company" uses a cookie to store your visiting and referrer information. A cookie is a small text file, stored on your computer's hard drive, that can be read by our system when you return to our site. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. 

## Children

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 18 and our Site is not targeted at children under the age of 18. 

## Third Party Websites

The Site may contain links to third-party websites for your convenience and information. We do not control those websites or make any representations or warranties about their use or the third party policies that govern such use. Any personal information that is obtained by third parties is not covered by this privacy policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of third-party websites. 

## Email

If you purchase software from us, your email address may be stored in our software registration server. Use of your email address will be limited to extreme cases such as administrative and identification purposes, notifying users of serious bugs in an application or very important updates/releases of our software. 

## Security

We use SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) security protection by encrypting all of your personal information to prevent individuals from reading this information as it travels over the Internet. We maintain reasonable and appropriate security procedures, but we cannot guarantee that your information will be secure in every circumstance. 

## Disclosures

Other than the disclosures referred to in this policy, we will not disclose any personal information without your permission unless we are legally obliged or entitled to do so. We will only disclose your personal information to a third party either as part of a reorganization or a sale of the assets of "Bandicam Company", and/or having ensured that steps have been taken to ensure that your privacy rights continue to be protected. 

## Forum

We offer you the ability to post information and exchange ideas. All users shouldn't disclose any personal information as part of their posts, even if requested to do so by other posters. "Bandicam Company" will not be responsible in the event that you disclose personal information in your posts or during any other communication with other site users. 

## Changes

"Bandicam Company" will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect company and customer feedback or changes to privacy legislation. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to be informed of how "Bandicam Company" is protecting your personal information. 

*** Related FAQ**  
\- 

_End User License Agreement and Terms of Service_
